GOTTARDELLC VALENTINA

Junior Software Developer

- 049 3258 402

PROFILE

I am web developer with a professional background and international experiences, I have cultivated valuable skills that make me a strong fit for the field of Software Engineering. I prioritize adaptability to new challenges and changes, and maintain a strong work ethic as integral aspects of my professional values.

BACK END

nede Node.js

express Express

PostgreSQL

Firebase

MongoDB

GraphQL

EXTRA TOOLS

Git

GitHub

Postman

Xcode

MongoDB Compas

SKILLS

FRONT END

НТМІ





React Js



React Native

TypeScript

Tailwind CSS

Material UI

Bootstrap

SASS

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY Computer Software Engineering Feb 2023 - May 2023

CODERHOUSE Web Developer Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CORDOBA Associates Degree, Law Mar 2012 - Dec 2017

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

GOOGLE TRANSLATE CLONE APP

· A user-friendly React TypeScript-based app, integrated with OpenAl API, offering seamless translations between multiple languages.

FIXUP

- · A work space app tailored for small businesses.
- · Full-stack application with React on the client-side, Express & PostgreSQL on the server-side, and deployed on Vercel.

MOVIESPLUS

- · Movies search app with user registration and saved movies list functionality.
- · Full-stack application using React, Tailwind, Apollo, GraphQL & MongoDB.

CONTACT MANAGMENT

- · App to efficiently manage imported contacts from various devices, enabling import, storage, editing, and deletion of Vcard files.
- · Full-stack application developed with React Native, Node, and Postgresgl.

PLAN MY PLATE

- · Meal planning app with integration of third-party APIs.
- · Built using React and Firebase, and deployed on Netlify.

TALKER'S

- · A powerful CRUD web application with a database backend.
- · Developed using JavaScript, Express, Ejs, Postgresgl, and NPM dependencies.

MOBILIA BUISNESS

- · Static web page showcasing Mobilia Furniture Business.
- · Built with HTML, CSS, SASS, and Bootstrap.

MORE EXPERIENCE CUSTOMER SERVICE STAFF

BARTENDER - Brooklyn Cocktail Bar

Melborune, Australia - Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

- Participated in the creation of the cocktails menu.
- Provided and guaranteed high-level customer service.
- Attention and resolution of problems under pressure.

TEAM LEAD & HEAD COACH - Beat Community Fitness Cordoba, Argentina - Mar 2019 - Jun 2021

- Leading classes and providing high-quality coaching to members.
- Create and update workout programs that challenge members appropriately while ensuring scalability and inclusivity.
- Hiring, training, and evaluating coaches and other gym staff members fall under the Team Lead's purview.

PARALEGAL - Boetto Law Firm

Cordoba, Argentina - Jan 2014 - Jul 2018

- Conducting extensive research.
- Assisting in the preparation of legal documents, such as contracts, pleadings, motions, briefs, and other legal correspondence.
- Interacting with clients, and other involved parties to gather information, schedule meetings, and provide updates on case progress.

LANGUAGE

- SPANISH Native or bilingual proficiency
- ENGLISH Full professional proficiency
- ITALIAN Professional working proficiency